stacksandstacks.com 2018-10-25

# Privacy and Security

|    

* * *

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions  

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

  * To send periodic emails  

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Our Shopping Cart features Thawte Secure SSL Encryption Security, to keep your information safe. Our Thawte Secure SSL Certificate features extended validation, or EV. You'll know your cart is secure when the address bar in your browser turns green. EV provides more security for personal information than standard SSL encryption. Information you enter is encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database and is only accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems. 

After a transaction, your credit cards numbers are not even stored on our servers. 

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information about your session while on our site. 

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

We may, from time to time use third party cookies, however these never track personal or identifiable information. We only use these to provide anonymous, behavioral information such as click stream data. 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page. 

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

### Microsoft Display Advertising

We currently do not participate in Microsoft Display Advertising Program so no information is being passed to Microsoft from us. 

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy. 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

This policy was last modified on 10/5/2016 

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.   
2523 Product Court   
Rochester Hills, Michigan 48309   
United States   
info@organizeit.com   
248-299-3350 

Our site maintains full SSL encryption security and is tested daily for vulnerabilities by TrustGuard. This service preforms an in depth analysis of our site and our server to make sure it is secure from hackers.  
  
---|---
